Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXIV is arranged in 1249 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXIV. LOCAL LODGES
  - Sub-Series 235-0. Local Lodges
    - General, 1958-1960 (Box 117, Folder 9)
      Jan. 1, 1958-March 31, 1960.
    - General, 1954-1957 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      Dec. 1954-Dec. 31, 1957.
    - General, 1954 (Box 117, Folder 11)
      July 1954-Nov. 1954.
    - General, 1952-1954 (Box 117, Folder 12)
      1952-June 1954.
    - General, 1922-1938 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - General, 1947-1950 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 235-3. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3, Omaha Lodge, Omaha, Nebraska, 1921-1949 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 235-4. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 4, Newark, New Jersey, 1921-1935 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      Suspended 1935
  - Sub-Series 235-6. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6, Fort William, Ontario, Canada, 1941-1944 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      Consolidated with Lodge 650 effective Dec. 1, 1944
    - Lodge No. 6, Nashville, Tennessee, 1928-1940 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      Suspended Dec. 11, 1940
  - Sub-Series 235-8. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 8, Victor Lodge, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1921-1959 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-9. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 9, Savannah Lodge, Savannah, Georgia, 1923-1959 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      1923-Dec. 31, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-10. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 10, Roosevelt Lodge, Hudson Court Bayonne, New Jersey, 1931-1958 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      Transferred to Lodge No. 975 effective April 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-11. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 11, Kingsville Lodge, Kingsville, Texas, 1922-1962 (Box 118, Folder 10)
      Consolidated with Lodges 67, 84, 901, 1080 effective July 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-15. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 15, Mahoney Lodge, Charleston, South Carolina, 1941-1967 (Box 118, Folder 11)
      Consolidated with Lodge 550 effective July 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-19. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 19, Dallas Texas and Pacific Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1932-1956 (Box 118, Folder 12)
      1932-Dec. 31, 1956.
  - Sub-Series 235-20. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 20, Union Station Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1921-1956 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1956.
  - Sub-Series 235-21. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 21, Danbury Lodge, Danbury, Connecticut, 1922-1962 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 14 effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-22. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 22, Knoxville Lodge, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1921-1962 (Box 118, Folder 15)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-24. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 24, Lookout Lodge, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1921-1962 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 235-25. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 25, Pontoosuc Lodge, Pittsfield, Massachusetts, 1932-1941 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 273 effective Aug. 22, 1941
  - Sub-Series 235-26. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 26, Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1922-1962 (Box 118, Folder 18)
      Consolidated with Lodges 464 and 1627 effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-28. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 28, Houston, Texas, 1922-1960 (Box 118, Folder 19)
      1922-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-29. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 29, Benton Harbor Lodge, Benton Harbor, Michigan, 1922-1962 (Box 118, Folder 20)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 810 effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-30. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 30, Southern California Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1954-1960 (Box 118, Folder 21)
      1954-Dec. 31, 1960.
    - Lodge No. 30, Southern California Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1948-1953 (Box 118, Folder 22)
      June 1948-53.
    - Lodge No. 30, Southern California Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1922-1948 (Box 118, Folder 23)
      1922-May 1948.
  - Sub-Series 235-36. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 36, Harmony Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1933-1960 (Box 118, Folder 24)
      1933-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-37. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 37, Beacon Lodge, Nashua, New Hampshire, 1949-1961 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 27 effective April 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-39. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 39, Cincinnati Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1922-1925 (Box 119, Folder 2)
      Disbanded in 1925
  - Sub-Series 235-42. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 42, Egypt Lodge, Cairo, Illinois, 1922-1959 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      Consolidated with Lodges 2055, 1175, 752, 642 and 65 effective Jan. 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-44. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 44, Frisco Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1958 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      1922-Dec. 31, 1958.
    - Lodge No. 44, Frisco Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1959-1962 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      Jan. 1, 1959-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-45. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 45, San Joaquin Division Lodge, Bakersfield, California, 1925-1958 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      1925-Dec. 31, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 235-46. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 46, Progress Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1926-1966 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      Disbanded effective Aug. 17, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-47. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 47, Fort Harrison Lodge, Terre Haute, Indiana, 1922-1957 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 675 effective Jan. 1, 1957
  - Sub-Series 235-48. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 48, Missouri Pacific Service Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1963 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 25 effective July 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-51. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 51, Somerville Lodge, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1922-1929 (Box 119, Folder 10)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 119, effective 1929?
  - Sub-Series 235-53. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 53, Old Reliable Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1961-1969 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      Jan. 1, 1961-69. Transferred to Lodges 1175 and 84 effective May 1, 1969
    - Lodge No. 53, Old Reliable Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1931-1960 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      1931-Dec. 31, 1960.
    - Lodge No. 53, Old Reliable Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1921-1930 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 235-56. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 56, Chelsea Lodge, New York City, New York, 1932-1959 (Box 119, Folder 14)
      1932-Dec. 31, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-60. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 60, Piasa Lodge, Alton, Illinois, 1922-1966 (Box 119, Folder 15)
      Consolidated with Lodges 642, 1024, and 2083 effective April 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-62. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 62, Wheeling and Lake Erie Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1924-1960 (Box 119, Folder 16)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1106 effective Sept. 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-63. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 63, Knickerbocker Lodge, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1934-1939 (Box 119, Folder 23)
      Consolidated with various lodges effective March 23, 1939
  - Sub-Series 235-66. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 66, Northampton Lodge, Northampton, Massachusetts, 1943 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 235-68. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 68, Chicago, Illinois, 1961-1969 (Box 119, Folder 17)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 333 effective Jan. 1, 1969
    - Lodge No. 68, New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1931-1960 (Box 119, Folder 22)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 143 effective Sept. 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-69. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 69, Southern Lodge, Richmond, Virginia, 1922-1962 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      1922-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-70 (Section 1). Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 70, New Haven Lodge, New York City, New York, 1922-1960 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 235-71. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 71, General Office Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1923-1958 (Box 119, Folder 20)
      1923-Dec. 31, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 235-75. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 75, Fort Worth Lodge, Fort Worth, Texas, 1958-1962 (Box 119, Folder 24)
      Jan. 1, 1958-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 75, Fort Worth Lodge, Fort Worth, Texas, 1929-1957 (Box 119, Folder 25)
      1929-Dec. 31, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-77. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 77, New River Lodge, Radford, Virginia, 1938-1961 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 711 effective July 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-80. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 80, Seminole Lodge, Birmingham, Alabama, 1945-1958 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1043 effective July 1, 1959
    - Lodge No. 80, Central Building Lodge, New York City, New York, 1921-1959 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 235-82. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 82, Danville Lodge, Danville, Illinois, 1923-1956 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      1923-Dec. 31, 1956.
  - Sub-Series 235-83. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 83, Erie Lodge, Kent, Ohio, 1935-1964 (Box 120, Folder 5)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 238 effective April 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-84. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 84, San Jacinto Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1922-1950 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 235-88. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 88, Manchester Lodge, Manchester, New Hampshire, 1931-1961 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 27 effective Feb. 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-90. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 90, Sunrise Lodge, North Bellmore, New York, 1921-1961 (Box 120, Folder 8)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 235-94. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 94, Progressive Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1944-1969 (Box 120, Folder 9)
      Transferred members to Lodge No. 943 effective June 1, 1969
    - Lodge No. 94, Hiawatha Lodge, Mason City, Iowa, 1922-1958 (Box 120, Folder 10)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 675 effective April 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-95. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 95, East Toledo Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1934-1957 (Box 120, Folder 11)
      1934-Dec. 31, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-97. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 97, Missouri-Kansas-Texas Lodge, St. Louis, Illinois, 1930-1960 (Box 120, Folder 12)
      1930-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-102. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 102, Georgia Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1924-1962 (Box 120, Folder 13)
      1924-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-103. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 103, Providence Lodge, Providence, Rhode Island, 1926-1957 (Box 120, Folder 14)
      1926-Dec. 31, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-104. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 104, Jacksonville Lodge, Jacksonville, Florida, 1943-1961 (Box 120, Folder 15)
      1943-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 235-105. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 105, Steadman Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1926-1963 (Box 120, Folder 16)
      1926-Dec. 31, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 235-107. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 107, Nutmeg State Lodge, New London, Connecticut, 1922-1961 (Box 120, Folder 17)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1095 effective March 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-108. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 108, Spindle City Lodge, Lowell, Massachusetts, 1929-1962 (Box 120, Folder 18)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 462 effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-109. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 109, St. Joseph Lodge, St. Joseph, Missouri, 1936-1954 (Box 120, Folder 19)
      1936-Dec. 31, 1954.
    - Lodge No. 109, St. Joseph Lodge, St. Joseph, Missouri, 1922-1935 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 235-110. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 110, Niagara Lodge, Niagara Falls, New York, 1935-1937 (Box 120, Folder 21)
      Transferred to Lodge No. 944 effective Sept. 22, 1937
    - Lodge No. 110, Santa Fe Trail Lodge, LaJunta, Colorado, 1930 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 235-116. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 116, Utica Lodge, Utica, New York, 1922-1949 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 235-120. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 120, Chicago and North Western General Office Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1923-1959 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 235-122. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 122, St. Lawrence Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1956-1962 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      Disbanded Jan. 16, 1962
    - Lodge No. 122, Augusta, Georgia, 1944-1955 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      Consolidated with Lodges 550 and 1027 effective July 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-123. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 123, Freight Handlers Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1959 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 44 effective July 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-124. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Ruffin et al v. Lodge # 124, 1961-1962 (Box 121, Folder 5)
      Lawsuit
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-"$300.00 Lodge No. 124, Special Working Fund", 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Suit against officers of this Lodge by Beward, Zawada, et al, 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Discipline against former members of Lodges 100, 1352, 6294 and 6319, 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Discipline Cases, 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      Date and numerical order
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Beward v. Uhland Case, Exhibits, 1956 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Material left in desk by H. B. Hassenger, 1954-1957 (Box 121, Folder 11)
      Retired Oct. 1, 1957
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Mailing list of former officers and members of the Local Protective Committees of defunct Lodge 100, 1352, 6294, and 6319 suspended from membership., 1956 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Joseph F. McGovern, Suit, 1957-1958 (Box 121, Folder 13)
      June 1957-58.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania-Joseph F. McGovern, Suit, 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 14)
      1956-May 1957.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 121, Folder 15)
      Jan. 1, 1964-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 16)
      Jan. 1, 1963-Dec. 31, 1963.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1960-1962 (Box 121, Folder 17)
      June 1, 1960-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1958-1960 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      Sept. 1958-May 31, 1960.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      Feb. 1958-Aug. 1958.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1957-1958 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      July 1957-Jan. 1958.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      Feb. 1957-June 1957.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1956-1957 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      Dec. 1956-Jan. 1957.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1956 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      Sept. 12, 1956-Nov. 1956.
    - Lodge No. 124, Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1954-1956 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      1954-Sept. 11, 1956.
    - Lodge No. 124, Rotterdam Junction Lodge, Mechanicville, New York, 1930-1949 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 12 effective July 1, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-125. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 125, Chicago Tunnel Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1922-1959 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 342 effective April 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-127. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 127, Agency Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1940-1968 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      Consolidated with Lodges 113, 339, 468, 679, 903, and 1240 effective April 1, 1968
    - Lodge No. 127, Queen City Lodge, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1930-1939 (Box 122, Folder 11)
      Suspended Oct. 4, 1939
    - Lodge No. 127, Augusta Lodge, Augusta, Georgia, 1923 (Box 122, Folder 12)
      Consolidated ?
  - Sub-Series 235-131. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 131, Wynne Lodge, Wynne, Arkansas, 1922-1953 (Box 122, Folder 13)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 730 effective Oct. 1, 1953
  - Sub-Series 235-132. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 132, Clear Lake Lodge, Springfield, Illinois, 1921-1961 (Box 122, Folder 14)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 283 effective July 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-133. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 133, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1931-1937 (Box 122, Folder 15)
      Suspended 1937
  - Sub-Series 235-135. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 135, Monroe Lodge (changed from Charlotte Lodge), Monroe, North Carolina, 1927-1956 (Box 122, Folder 16)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 16 effective July 1, 1956 / New Lodge No. 135, Canada effective 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-137. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 137, Des Moines Lodge, Des Moines, Iowa, 1921-1957 (Box 122, Folder 17)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-142. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 142, Texas and Pacific Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1926-1964 (Box 122, Folder 18)
      Consolidated with Lodges 19, 57, 75, 356, 465, 769, 1260, and 1722 effective April 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-143. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 143, Old Colony Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1921-1961 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 235-148. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 148, Twin City Lodge, Texarkana, Texas, 1921-1929 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      Disbanded
  - Sub-Series 235-153. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 153, Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, 1938 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      Disbanded Dec. 27, 1938
    - Lodge No. 153, Hearne, Texas, 1925 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 235-154. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 154, Onward Lodge, Trenton, New Jersey, 1922-1962 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 235-157. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 157, Nebraska Lodge, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1921-1959 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 235-159. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 159, Boomer Lodge, Stillwater, Oklahoma, 1921 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 235-161. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 161, Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal (B. & O. C. T. ) Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1933-1961 (Box 122, Folder 22)
      1933-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 235-162. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 162, Dearborn Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1922-1965 (Box 122, Folder 23)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 204 effective April 1, 1965
  - Sub-Series 235-163. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1954-1955 (Box 122, Folder 24)
      Subject: Willie M. Fisher
    - Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1954-1957 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      Subject: Shortage, M.P. McMahon
    - 235-163 (Section 3). Supervision of Local Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1953-1958 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      Oct. 1953-58.
    - 235-163 (Section 2). Supervision of Local Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1953 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      May 1953-Sept 1953.
    - 235-163 (Section 1). Supervision of Local Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1952-1953 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      1952-April 1953.
    - Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1955-1959 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      Dec. 1955-Dec. 31, 1959.
    - Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1954-1955 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      June 16, 1954-Nov. 1955.
    - Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1953-1954 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      Nov. 1953-June 15, 1954.
    - Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1952-1953 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      April 1952-Oct. 1953.
    - Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1951-1952 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      1951-March 1952.
    - Lodge No. 163, Baggage Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1929-1950 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 235-164. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 164, Pennsylvania Terminal Lodge, New York City, New York, 1923-1959 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 235-167. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 167, Illinois Lodge, Springfield, Illinois, 1921-1955 (Box 123, Folder 15)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1955.
  - Sub-Series 235-168. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 168, Milwaukee Junction Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1936-1960 (Box 123, Folder 16)
      1936-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-173. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 173, Palisade Lodge, Weehawken, New Jersey, 1960-1962 (Box 123, Folder 17)
      April 1, 1960-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-175. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 175, Stroudsburg Lodge, Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania, 1921-1961 (Box 123, Folder 18)
      Consolidated with Lodges 949 and 2023 effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-176. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 176, Yadkin Lodge, Salisbury, North Carolina, 1921-1957 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 235-177. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 177, Long Island Lodge, Jamaica, New York, 1921-1962 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 235-178. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 178, George E. Evans Lodge, Louisville, Kentucky, 1921-1955 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 235-180. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 180, Golden Rod Lodge, Illmo, Missouri, 1922-1961 (Box 123, Folder 22)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1366 effective July 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-181. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 181, High Springs Lodge, High Springs, California, 1941-1969 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodges 1220, 1523, 1420 effective April 1, 1969
    - Lodge No. 181, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1938-1939 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      Suspended Jan. 10, 1941
    - Lodge No. 181, Cadillac Lodge, Cadillac, Michigan, 1929-1934 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 235-182. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 182, Colton Lodge, Colton, California, 1938-1967 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1376 effective July 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-183. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 183, Garden City Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1921-1958 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 216 effective July 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-184. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 184, Santa Fe Lodge, Dodge City, Kansas, 1923-1964 (Box 124, Folder 5)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 179 effective July 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-187. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 187, Marquette Lodge, Marquette, Michigan, 1921-1958 (Box 124, Folder 6)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 235-188. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 188, Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railway Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1933-1959 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 68 effective Jan. 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-189. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 189, Benjamin Franklin Lodge, New York City, New York, 1922-1960 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 235-191. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 191, Montreal Harbour Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1940-1965 (Box 124, Folder 11)
      Disbanded effective Oct. 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-192. Local Lodges